nylonmag.com 2018-12-26

# NYLON · NYLON MEDIA PRIVACY POLICY

**Effective:**   
May 18, 2015 

**On our site we collect the following:**

  * Name
  * Address
  * Email address
  * Phone number
  * Payment information
  * Any other information that you voluntarily provide

**Personally identifying information is collected from you when you:**

  * Register on our site, subscribe to our magazine or make a purchase in our shop

**The information collected from you is used in the following ways:**

  * To personalize user’s experience and analyze the usage of our site
  * To administer contests, promotions, surveys or other site features
  * To send periodic emails
  * To provide and market this site and Nylon’s products and services
  * To respond to your questions and requests

**How do we protect visitor information?**

  * We use vulnerability scanning on certain parts of our site
  * We use session encryption when taking payments
  * We implement security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their sensitive personal information
  * We use a payment gateway provider

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes, we do use cookies and other technologies for analytics, marketing and other purposes. More information about how our site uses Google Analytics to collect and analyze information is available [here](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/). We also work with third-party advertising companies who use cookies or other technology to collect non-personally identifiable information on our site in order to provide advertisements on our site and on third-party websites. These third parties may collect information about your online activities over time and across different websites. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based advertising or other targeted content. We do not provide these third parties with your personally identifiable information ( _e.g._ , name, address, email address) unless you give us permission. We do not honor any “do not track” signals from your browser. 

**Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties for their own marketing purposes without your permission. We may disclose your personal information to our agents, affiliates and other third parties that perform functions on our behalf, help use maintain and run this site, or help us provide or market our products and services. 

In addition, we may transfer some or all of your information to an entity that acquires all or part of our company or if there is a change in ownership. We may also use or disclosure your personal information if required to do so by law or on the good-faith believe that such action is necessary to comply with applicable law, legal process, or to protect or defend our rights or our users. 

**Third party links**

We are not responsible for any third-party products, services, or websites that are linked to on our site. 

**Google**

We have not enabled Google AdWords on our site but we may do so on the future. 

**Users will be notified of any privacy policy changes:**

  * Via email, if available, and the revised policy will be posted to this site. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy from time to time without advance notice. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes will mean you accept those changes.

**Users are able to change their personal information:**

  * By logging in to their account

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act) 

We do not specifically market to children under 13. 

**If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future marketing emails, you can:**

  * Email us at [privacy@nylon.com](http://mailto:privacy@nylon.com/) and we will promptly remove you from ALL marketing emails.

**Contact Information**

NYLON  
Attn: Website Privacy  
110 Greene Street, #600  
New York, NY 10012
